<resources>
    <!-- Title for the app.-->
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideZagreb</string>

    <!-- Name for the eat category -->
    <string name="eat_category">Eat</string>

    <!-- Name for the sleep category -->
    <string name="sleep_category">Sleep</string>

    <!-- Name for the visit category -->
    <string name="visit_category">Visit</string>

    <!-- Name for the see category -->
    <string name="see_category">See</string>

    <string name="info_title">INFO</string>

    <!-- Content for the eat category -->

    <!-- Restaurant AbOvo -->
    <string name="restaurant_ab_ovo">AbOvo</string>
    <string name="des_ab_ovo_">Our concept is based on daily changing menu.
        In our kitchen every day presents new beginning.
        We work exclusively with fresh and local ingredients of known and verified origin.
        $$-$$$
        Mediterranean, European</string>
    <string name="info_la_ab_ovo">Phone: +385 1 4678 554
        Address: Bukovačka 27
        10 000 Zagreb
        E-mail: abovobistro@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- Restaurant La Struk -->
    <string name="restaurant_la_struk">La Struk</string>
    <string name="des_la_struk">La Štruk serves only traditional Croatian specialty – štrukli,
        a unique traditional Croatian dish served in most households across Hrvatsko Zagorje
        and Zagreb. It is made from special dough and fresh cow cheese.
        $
        Croatian, Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="info_la_struk">Phone: +385 1 4837 701
        Address:Skalinska 5
        10000 Zagreb
        E-mail: lastruk.zg@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Rocket Burger -->
    <string name="restaurant_rocket">Rocket Burger</string>
    <string name="des_rocket_burger">Rocket Burger is an American style Diner,
        bringing burgers back to their basic form before fast food chains took them over.
        $
        American, Fast Food</string>
    <string name="info_rocket_burger">Phone: +385 1 4845 386
        Address: Tkalčićeva 50
        E-mail: rocketburgerhr@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Zinfandels -->
    <string name="restaurant_zinfandel">Zinfandels Restaurant</string>
    <string name="des_zinfandel">Zinfandel’s is widely regarded as the one of the best Zagreb restaurants.
        Its innovative cuisine in a delightful setting includes terrace views and alfresco dining options.
        $$$$
        Contemporary, Croatian</string>
    <string name="info_zinfandel">Phone: +385 1 4566 644
        Address: Mihanovićeva 1
        E-mail: zinfandels@esplanade.hr</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Zrno -->
    <string name="restaurant_zrno">Zrno bio bistro</string>
    <string name="des_zrno">First certified 100% organic vegan restaurant in Zagreb.
        We offer organic ingredients delivered each day directly from Croatias first organic
        farm Zrno and warm sourdough bread from our own bakery.
        $-$$
        Organic, Vegan</string>
    <string name="info_zrno">Phone: +385 1 4847 540
        Address: Medulićeva 20
        E-mail: restoran@bio-zrno.hr</string>

    <!-- Content for the sleep category -->
    <!-- Hotel Esplanade -->
    <string name="hotel_esplanade">Hotel Esplanade</string>
    <string name="five_stars">*****</string>
    <string name="des_esplanade">Beautifully designed rooms blended with the delicate combination of
        Art Deco heritage and contemporary touches. A long history of first-class service,
        spectacular facilities and simply amazing food at a price you can afford.
        Experience the true essence of luxury. Discover the iconic Esplanade Zagreb Hotel.
        Address: Mihanovićeva 1, 10000 Zagreb, Croatia
        Phone: +385 1 4566 666
        E-mail: info@esplanade.hr</string>

    <!-- Hotel DoubleTree -->
    <string name="hotel_doubletree">DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Zagreb</string>
    <string name="four_stars">****</string>
    <string name="des_doubletree">Ideally located in the heart of Zagrebs business district and
        two kilometers from the historic city center, our award-winning DoubleTree by Hilton Zagreb
        hotel is set within the Green Gold complex, offering great shopping and dining options.
        Address: Ulica Grada Vukovara 269a, Zagreb, 10000, Croatia
        Phone: +385-1-6001900</string>

    <!-- Hotel Palace -->
    <string name="hotel_palace">Hotel Palace</string>
    <string name="des_palace">The Palace Hotel Zagreb, located in the centre of the palace
        immediately next to the old city park, opened its doors in 1907 as the first official
        hotel in Zagreb. The hotel successfully combines the comfort of a modern lifestyle
        with a warm retro-chic atmosphere created by its stylish furniture and modernist interior.
        Address:Trg J.J. Strossmayera 10
        Phone: +385 1 4899 600
        E-mail: palace@palace.hr</string>

    <!-- Hotel Priča -->
    <string name="hotel_prica">Hotel Priča</string>
    <string name="three_stars">***</string>
    <string name="des_prica">I guess my English name would be The Story Hotel, because story
        means a\priča\ in Croatian. I got this name for being the only known hotel that talks
        to its guests. a\Priča\ also means talks. All of my stories are nice and have a happy ending,
        there is a lot of laughter, dancing, giggling, hugging and smiling going on…
        Address: Samoborska cesta 214, 10436 Rakov Potok, Croatia
        Phone: +385 1 6586 053
        E-mail:hotel@hotelprica.com</string>

    <!-- Hostel Swanky -->
    <string name="hotel_swanky">Hostel Swanky</string>
    <string name="two_stars">**</string>
    <string name="des_swanky">The Swanky Mint is a renovated factory dating back to the
        late 19th century. Combining the industrial machinery that littered the site with
        new technology, the Mint has created a comfortable eco-friendly atmosphere that makes it
        a very special place to visit. Private rooms, separate apartments, bed and breakfast,
        dorm rooms big and small, all on offer here at unbeatable value.
        Address: Ilica 50, Zagreb 10000, Croatia
        Phone:+385 (01) 4004 248
        Email: mint@swanky-hostel.com</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>


